

### CONTACT

- anhviet.key@gmail.com
- (+84) 349423372
- Quang Ngai

#### **SKILLS**

HTML/CSS

**JAVASCRIPT** 

**REACTJS** 

VUEJS

**NODEJS** 

## **ORTHER SKILLS**

Nextjs, Typescript, Redux, Sass, Bootstrap, TailWind, Mysql, MongoDB, Go

#### INTERESTS

Football, badminton Read comics Watch movie ...

### Certification

Responsive Web Design freecodecamp.org

Mar 2022

<u>Javascript bassic</u> <u>fullstack.vn</u> Apr 2022

## **NGUYEN ANH VIET**

FRESHER FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### **SUMMARY**

Be an enthusiastic, dynamic, responsible person at work. Constantly learning to cultivate old and new knowledge about programming to develop more professional skills. With the current knowledge, there are many shortcomings I want to find a suitable and long-term workplace along with supplementing the missing knowledge. In the next two years, I will become a full-stack programmer.

### **EDUCATION**

Sep 2019 - Jun 2022

# Vietnam Korea University of Information and Communication Technology

Bachelor's degree: 3.12 (Decent category)

## **Experience**

Intern Sep 2022 - Oct 2022

- FADO Joint Stock Company (Fado group)
- Mission: Learn new languages, perform assigned tasks, and take courses to improve their knowledge.
- Programming Languages: Golang, redis, react, typescript

Project Mar 2022 - Apr 2022 Online learning websites through video courses

- omine rearring websites through video courses
- Mission: Full stack, build the necessary functions. Responsive applications and Grid System design interfaces suitable for all devices.
- Programming Languages: Html, css, php, javascript

Project Now 2021 - Dec 2021 Website selling laptops

- Mission: Refer to available templates, design interfaces, learn MVC model structures, and program some product management functions.
- Programming Languages: Html, css, php, javascript

## **Activity**

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022

#### Volunteer

- Give gifts to disadvantaged students
- Participate in organizing fun activities at school
- Collect garbage at the campus and beaches.